My homeland...
My homeland!
Glory and beauty,
sublimity and splendor
are in your hills...
Are in your hills!
Life and deliverance,
pleasure and hope
are in your air...
Are in your air!
Will I see you, will I see you?
Safely comforted and victoriously honored...
Safely comforted and victoriously honored!
Will I see you?
In your eminence?
Reaching to the stars...
Reaching to the stars!
My homeland...
My homeland.
My homeland, my homeland!
The youth will not tire, 'till your independence.
Or they die...
Or they die!
We will drink from death, and will not be to our enemies
like slaves, like slaves.
We do not want, we do not want:
An eternal humiliation, nor a miserable life...
An eternal humiliation,
nor a miserable life.
We do not want,
but we will bring back:
Our storied glory...
Our storied glory!
My homeland...
My homeland!